

CONTACT



nikita.kotov.1404@gmail.com



+375333581622 (Calls only)



Belarus, Minsk Ready for relocation



linkedin.com/in/nikita-kotov-037389230

EDUCATIONS

Jan 2022 - Apr 2022 **SOFTWARE TEST ENGINEER** (Certificate) IT-Academy

Sept 2015 - June 2019 **BACHELOR'S DEGREE, MARKETING-ECONOMIST** International University "MITSO"

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH - B1 RUSSIAN - NATIVE BELARUSIAN - NATIVE

RECOMMENDATIONS

Iryna Malets, IT-Academy, Trainer

epam.iryna.koush@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/iryna-malets-43824586

Kotov Nikita

JUNIOR SOFTWARE TESTING ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

I'm Junior Software Testing Engineer with experience in web testing. I have theoretical experience in different software development methodologies. I'm also skilled in requirements analysis. I have experience in creating and maintaining various test documentation. I'm a team player who also have good interpersonal and commutation skills.

MY SKILLS

- Functional testing
- JIRA
- Non-functional Testing
 MySQL
- Test Cases
- Virtual Box
- Bug reporting
- Selenium IDE
- API Testing
- SoapUI
- Agile Methodologies
- Postman
- TestRail
- JMeter

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mar 2022 - Apr 2022 Work on a project at the IT-Academy **Software Testing Engineer**

Responsibilities:

- Writing test documentation
- Manual testing of application using different types and approaches of testing

Sept 2019 - Dec 2021 ООО "Стаут Инвест" Jackwood.by Director

Responsibilities:

- Conclusion of contracts (full cycle of sale)
- Implementation of projects.
- Search and attract partners for long-term cooperation.
- Hiring new employees and their adaptation.
- Development and launch of new project directions.

Accomplishments:

- More than 50 contracts have been signed.
- Implemented 93 projects together with the team.
- The staff was increased from 4 people to 12, including the creation of a sales department and the creation of a new position for a furniture designer company.
- Successfully launched a new direction of projects for the company, for the creation of glass products. 8 orders have been completed in this direction.